A fireworks festival.
（日代(ひしろ)）花火大会
友達と 一緒にお出かけ
Going out with friends!
（大神(おおが)）
俺 狩生(かりう)を 花火大会に誘って—
I'll invite Kariu to
the fireworks festival...
...and confess!
告白する！
So, uh...
What's up?
I'm...
...gonna tell Oga how I feel today.
Oga said he might go to college elsewhere.
（狩生）大神 外部の大学
受けるかもなんだって
And here I was taking it for granted
that we'd be together in college, too.
当たり前のように—
この先も一緒なんだろうって
思ってきたけど—
But if we end up separated,
I'll regret not saying anything.
もし 離れることになるなら—
言わなきゃ 後悔する気がする
So help make sure we're alone together!
だから それとなく２人きりに
なれるよう 協力して下さい
If you know you'll be separated...
（日代）離れることになるって
分かっていて—
...then falling in love...
好きになるなんて…
Understood.
...or confessing your feelings...
思いを告げるなんて—
Leave it to me!
...kind of seems pointless.
ムダではないですか？
Hishiro-san! Over here!
（海崎(かいざき)）日代さーん こっち
（日代）はあ すみません 皆さん
Sorry, everyone!
時間に遅れるなど 人として最低
There is nothing worse
a person can do than be late!
This failure can never be forgiven.
許されない失態…
（海崎）誰も３分の遅刻で
そこまで言ってないから
Nobody would ever say that to
someone three minutes late.
（玉来(たまらい)）大丈夫？ ひしろん
You okay, Hishiro?
は はい
Yes...
I've never been to a festival.
お祭りなんて 初めてで—
混雑の予測が まるで桁違いでした
I completely underestimated the crowd.
I can't apologize enough!
本当に申し訳ありません
（海崎）お祭り 初めてなんだ
Her first festival!
Confession
Frankfurters
Corn on the cob
Soba
Cold
Well, everyone's here.
（海崎）
じゃあ みんなそろったし—
日代さんが落ち着いたところで
行こっか
And Hishiro-san's calmed down. Let's go!
（小野屋(おのや)）新太(あらた)くーん
あたし たこ焼き食べたい
Arata-kun!
I'd love some takoyaki!
So buy some.
（海崎）食えば？
（小野屋）冷たっ
Meanie!
（海崎）
たこ焼きくらい 自分で買え！
You can afford takoyaki!
Aki-chan! Let's catch some goldfish again!
アキちゃん
今年も金魚すくい しよ
You're on.
（犬飼(いぬかい)）望むところだ
（朝地(あさじ)）また獲り尽くして
お店の人 困らせちゃダメだよ
Don't catch too many!
Remember last year? That poor stall owner.
（大神）いやあ 暑いね…
Man, it's hot.
（狩生）そうね…
Yeah.
You okay, Hishiro-san?
（夜明(よあけ)）日代さん 大丈夫？
How far'd you run?
結構 走ってきた
みたいだったけど—
Your feet hurt?
足 痛めてない？
My feet are fine.
足は何ともありません
But the crowd's a bit much,
and I'm a little dizzy.
少し 人混みに
酔ってしまったようで—
クラクラしてますが—
I'll be fine.
大丈夫です
Need an arm?
（夜明）腕 貸そうか？
See? Like them.
ほら あんな感じだよ
Keeps you from tripping, yeah?
コケないように ね？
You don't mind?
（日代）いいんですか？
俺が“いい”って
言ってるんだから
I offered, didn't I?
Then I will accept your offer.
では お言葉に甘えて
Look, we need to be subtle.
（海崎）いいか それとなーく だぞ
分かってますって〜
I know, I know.
Gotta leave those two alone naturally—
自然にあいつらを
２人っきりにして…
（海崎）えっ 何だあれ？
夜明さん まさか女子高生に…
What?
Is Yoake-san really making
a move on a high school girl?!
No, no, out of the question.
って いやいや それはねえだろう
Ryo...
Yoake-san might not be...
（海崎）
夜明さんはそうじゃなくても—
But could Hishiro-san be...?
日代さんは もしかして…
Huh? Where is everyone?
（大神）あれ みんなは？
もしかして—
Did we get separated?
（大神）はぐれちゃった？
（狩生）え？
Huh?
Enjoy your alone time!
（海崎）２人っきりになっただろ
（玉来）２人っきりになれたでしょ
Good luck!
（大神）ええ もう？
Already?!
（狩生）確かにお願いしたけど
こんな不意打ち
Sure, I asked for it,
but this came out of nowhere!
（狩生･大神）
気持ちが追いつかないって！
I'm not ready yet!
What are you doing, Tama?
タマ 何してんだ
Hurry up, or I'll catch them all.
早く来ねえと
俺が全部 獲っちまうぞ
（玉来）ああ アキちゃん ずるい
負けないよ！
Aw, no fair! I won't lose, though!
（店主）あんたら 去年の！
（朝地）すみませーん
You! From last year!
Sorry!
Distance to target: 1 meter.
It went well, huh?
うまくいきましたね
If gravitation force is g,
and my throw is at 180 degrees,
More importantly, do something about An!
そんなことより 杏(あん) 何とかしろよ
I need a force of...
She's being super clingy.
Will that math help?
やたら 引っついてくるんだけど
ふむ まあ職員と被験者が
２人っきりで—
Hmm... it would be a problem
if we had a subject
まったく学生と関わらないのは
困りますが—
and an employee hanging out,
ignoring the students.
But everyone's here today, so it's fine!
今日の場合 みんないますし—
（夜明）いっかなって
（海崎）ゆるっ
You're lax!
Oh, I see.
（夜明）ああ そっか
You aren't bothered by Onoya.
小野屋がどうこうじゃなくて—
僕が 日代さんといたのが
お気に召さないんですか
You don't like me being with Hishiro-san.
うっ
そんなんじゃねえよ
10 cm diameter.
That's not it!
You should have said!
（夜明）そうならそうと
言ってくれればいいのに
Pi is 3.14...
Will those calculations really help?
すみません 配慮が足らず
Sorry, I didn't even notice.
Quiet, please.
Like I said...
（海崎）だから…
（夜明）高校最後の夏
It's the last summer of high school.
It's a precious time that won't come again.
（夜明）二度と来ない貴重な時間
なんでしょ？
ま 海崎さんにとっては—
But I guess for you,
最初で最後の夏ですけどね
this is your first and last summer!
You... god damn sadist!
（海崎）この クソどＳ
So what am I supposed to do about it?
だったら どうしろっつうんだよ
Can't wait for the fireworks!
（大神）花火… 楽しみだね
Say, Kariu.
（大神）ねえ 狩生
好き… なんですけど
I, uh... love you.
Out of the blue?!
いきなり？ しかも
こんな人通りの多いとこで？
With all these people around?!
Not good timing?
タイミング 間違えた
Not exactly, no.
それも そうだけど…
But that's not the point...
そうじゃなくて…
What?!
（狩生）
何なの？ こんな展開 聞いてない
Nobody told me this would happen!
そうくるとは 思わないじゃん
I didn't think he'd do that!
（狩生）思わないじゃん！
I didn't think you'd do this!
Are you... serious?
（狩生）本気… で言ってんの？
（大神）何？ 信用できない？
What? You don't trust me?
（狩生）
ち 違う！ 信じられないだけで…
N-Not that! I just can't believe it!
（大神）それ 意味 一緒でしょ
That's the same thing, isn't it?
No.
（狩生）違う…
そういう… 意味じゃなくて…
I didn't mean it like that.
Man, I came up with so many ideas.
ああ もう いろいろ考えてたのに
こんなはずじゃなかったのに
It wasn't supposed to go like this!
（狩生）あっ
（大神）狩生！
Kariu!
Oh, sorry.
（男性）あ ごめんなさい
When you asked me to these
fireworks, I was so happy.
（狩生）あたし—
大神から 今日の花火に
誘われて うれしかった
Oga...
大神 外部の大学
行くかもしれないって—
I remembered you talking about
going to college elsewhere.
言ってたの 思い出して—
So I made up my mind to tell you today.
今日 言おうって 決めてた
I've been in love with you
since our first year, too.
あたしも １年の頃から
ずっと好きでした
つきあってください
Will you go out with me?
Come on! I summon all my courage to
tell you, and that's how you react?!
（狩生）人が 超 勇気出して
告白してるのに—
何よ そのリアクション！
いや 普通 驚くでしょ！
I mean, who wouldn't be surprised?
告白しようと思ってたら
されるとか 驚くでしょ！
I was gonna ask you out,
but you asked me instead!
そっくりそのまま 返すわよ！
Right back at you!
Ow...
（大神）痛い…
Sorry.
（大神）ごめんね 俺 何だろう
I... how should I put this?
I've never really talked about
these things with friends.
昔からあんまり 友達と—
そういう話を
してこなかったから—
こういうの 鈍いところあると思う
I think I'm not good
at picking up on things.
I had no idea you felt that way.
狩生の気持ち 全然気づかなかった
I didn't notice how I felt, either.
自分の気持ちにも
全然気づいてなかった
Not until Arata gave me a push.
新太に言われて やっと自覚した
狩生がいないと つまらないなって
I thought that without you,
everything would be so boring.
狩生が誰か
ほかの人に触られてんの—
The idea of someone else touching you...
was just not okay.
嫌だなって
I only realized this recently.
気づいたのは
ほんの最近だけど—
But I think...
俺もたぶん—
...I've loved you for a long time, too.
ずっと前から
狩生のこと 好きだったよ
うううっ 俺 今
結構 恥ずかしいこと言った？
Oh, man! That was really embarrassing!
時間差で照れないでよ
こっちが恥ずかしい
Don't get embarrassed on a delay!
You're making me blush!
Are these fireworks starting soon?
（大神）花火 そろそろかな
I think so.
（狩生）た たぶん
Um...
（大神）あの… 狩生… さん
Kariu-san.
Do you mind...
手を—
つないでも—
よろしいでしょうか？
...if we hold hands?
I... I don't mind.
よろしい です
（小野屋）
わあ 朝地君 シート 準備いい
Oh, Asaji-kun!
You brought a sheet!
（朝地）どうぞ〜
Sit down!
（犬飼）ああっ 蚊に刺された
A mosquito just bit me.
（朝地）
はい 薬 虫よけスプレーもしとく？
Here, medicine. Need some bug repellent?
What? Asaji-kun, are you our mom?
（小野屋）
何？ 朝地君って お母さん？
Huh? Where are Kaizaki-san and Hishiro-san?
（玉来）
あれ？ 海崎君と日代さんは？
Oh, yeah... who knows?
（夜明）そう言えば…
（朝地）どうしたんだろうね？
Oh... but the fireworks are starting!
ええ？ もう花火 始まっちゃうのに
（犬飼）タマも 虫よけしとけ
（玉来）はーい
Tama, you need bug spray?
Yep!
Huh? Where'd Yoake-kun and...
（海崎）あれ？
夜明… 君たちは？ あっ
But I guess for you, this is
your first and last summer!
海崎さんにとっては
最初で最後の夏ですけどね
They set me up, too?!
（海崎）俺も ハメられたのか！
（日代）ん？
Attention. Fireworks will begin soon.
（アナウンス）間もなく
打ち上げ開始時間となります…
Man, we're really boxed in here.
Please enjoy the beautiful fireworks
against the clear summer sky.
（海崎）こりゃ もう 動けないな
日代さん
Hishiro-san, wanna just watch from here?
（海崎）この辺で 見ていこうか
（日代）はい
Sure.
Ryo...
了…
Is he a friend of yours, Kaizaki-san?
と 仲がいいですよね 海崎さん
I've seen you talk at school, too.
学校でも たまに話してますし
Sure, I guess.
別に まあ 普通に友達かな
I guess we're friends.
そうですか
I see.
Kaizaki-san, you make friends
with everybody very easily.
確かに海崎さん 誰とでもすぐ—
（日代）仲よくなれますもんね
（海崎）え？
In April, you'd just enrolled,
まだ ４月の編入したての
頃から—
but you were already surrounded by friends.
すでに海崎さんは
友達の輪の中にいました
I remember seeing that and clearly thinking,
それを見て“私も頑張らないと”
と思ったことを—
"I've got to try harder."
とてもよく覚えています
Hishiro-san, you're here with everyone, too.
（海崎）
日代さんだって 今こうやって—
みんなと一緒に
花火に来てるじゃん
Seeing the fireworks.
はぐれちゃったけどさ
Except we got separated.
You're surrounded by friends,
too, Hishiro-san.
友達の輪の中にいるよ 日代さんも
You've tried plenty hard.
頑張ったんだね
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
主に海崎さんのおかげです
The credit is mostly yours.
I'm really glad I met you.
（日代）
海崎さんに出会えて よかったです
（玉来）わあ
（小野屋）きれい
Gorgeous!
（狩生）きれい
（大神）だねえ
Beautiful.
Yeah.
（狩生）けど左手が
（大神）けど右手が
But I'm so focused on my left hand,
I can barely watch the fireworks!
But I'm so focused on my right hand,
（狩生･大神）
気になっちゃって 正直—
花火どころじゃない！
I'm really glad I met you.
（日代）
海崎さんに出会えて よかったです
What did she mean by that?
（海崎）あれって どういう…
いやいや 何の気なしの言葉だろ
No, no, she meant nothing more.
そう思った相手なら 誰にでも
サラリと言うよ 日代さんなら
If she felt like it, Hishiro-san
would totally say that to anyone!
深い意味はない…
It doesn't mean anything.
Thanks.
ありがとう
そんなふうに 思ってくれて
For thinking of me that way.
それだけで—
That alone...
...makes me think this ReLIFE
was worth living.
俺のリライフに
意味があったように 思えてくるよ
Though you'll forget me.
忘れられてしまうけど…
They're lovely.
（日代）きれいですね
But there's something a little sad
about them, too.
（海崎）でも—
少し切ない感じもするよね
花火って
There is?
（日代）そうですか？
They're so flashy, pretty, and exciting,
but as they fade, you feel sort of lonely.
派手で きれいで
テンションあがる分—
消えちゃった時
何か寂しいっていうか
You're an illusion that's meant to fade away.
（夜明）どうせ消えてしまう幻
なんですし
When the experiment ends,
（海崎）実験が終われば—
この生活も終わる
so will this life.
They'll forget me.
みんな 忘れる
Including Hishiro-san.
日代さんも
They'll all forget me.
（海崎）俺のこと—
みんな 忘れる
They're so flashy, pretty, and exciting,
but as they fade, you feel sort of lonely.
（海崎）派手で きれいで
テンションあがる分—
消えちゃった時
何か寂しいっていうか…
Hishiro-san, you're here with everyone.
日代さんだって 今こうやって
みんなと一緒に…
友達の輪の中にいるよ
頑張ったんだね
Surrounded by friends.
You've tried plenty hard.
（日代）海崎さんに出会えて
よかったです
I'm glad I met you.
If you know you'll be separated...
it kind of seems pointless.
離れることになるって
分かっていて—
ムダではないですか？
告白… ですね
A confession?
了は去年 同じクラス…
Ryo was in my class last year.
そう呼んでと言われたので
He told me to call him that.
（海崎）日代さんから
声かけて…
It's not often that you start a conversation.
（日代）
はい 狩生さんと玉来さんに…
Yes. Kariu-san and Tamarai-san
gave them to me.
（夜明）日代さんから
声かけて…
It's not often that you start a conversation.
（狩生･玉来）
ひしろんのおかげだよ！
It's all thanks to you, Hishiro!
（日代）
経験から言えば お勧めはしません
I did that. I don't recommend it.
They're all irreplaceable.
お友達を大切にしてください
You can't turn back.
私のように
あきらめないで…
Don't give up like I did.
一緒にリベンジ
してくれませんか？
Let's get revenge.
Fight on!
Together.
私のクラスには
いじめがありました
You're in my class?
I'm changing.
（海崎）どんどん友達 増えて…
You have more friends.
（日代）許します
I forgive you. After all, we're friends.
友達… ですから
Can I have...
愛想笑いのひとつも
できないなんて—
A friendly smile.
...your phone?
Out in the real world...
社会に出たら きっと…
そこ 私の席なんですけど
That's my seat.
Congratulations!
（夜明）おめでとうございます
You've been selected as the
ReLIFE Laboratory Kanto Branch's
あなたは 我がリライフ研究所
関東支部の—
被験者第１号に選ばれました
test subject no. 001!
Nice to meet you, Hishiro Chizuru-san.
はじめまして 日代千鶴(ちづる)さん
After the ReLIFE period ends,
リライフの期間が終了したのち—
クラスメートや教師
関わったすべての人から—
classmates, teachers, and anyone
you dealt with will forget about you.
日代さんの記憶は消えます
The more fun I have,
the more it'll hurt when we part ways.
（日代）楽しませてくれる分—
離れる時は きっとつらい
I know that all too well.
分かりきってるはずなのに…
I know this is a bad idea.
ダメなのに…
（日代）海崎さんって
Kaizaki-san, you're like the fireworks.
（花火の音）
（日代）…なんですね
（海崎）え？ 何？
What?
Nothing, never mind.
いいえ 何でもないです
（海崎）あ 日代さん あれ
（日代）あ…
Hishiro-san, look!
海崎さん
Kaizaki-san...
（海崎）あは〜
（日代）すこぶるお顔が—
That face is really creepy.
気持ち悪いです
Huh?
〜♪
That was so much fun! Oga-kun, thank you!
（玉来）楽しかったあ
大神君 ありがとね
No, thank you.
（大神）こちらこそ ありがとう
（狩生）ふふ
See ya!
じゃあ またね
じゃあ 俺は
小野屋さんを送ってくんで—
Okay, I'll walk Onoya-san home!
新太は日代さんをお願い
（海崎）え？
Take care of Hishiro-san, Arata!
（夜明）方角的に
そのほうが適任でしょ？
You live in the same direction, right?
That's true. Kaizaki-san, do you mind?
そうですね
海崎さん お願いします
あ はい
Okay.
Kazu-kun, look after Kariu-san.
カズ君は 狩生さんを
お願いしますね
お おう！
Y-Yeah.
（夜明）僕が 日代さんといるのが
お気に召さないんですか
You don't like me being with Hishiro-san.
That's not true.
（海崎）そんなんじゃねえよ
珍しい組み合わせに
ちょっとびっくりしただけで…
I just never see them together.
It was surprising, that's all.
H-Hishiro-san?!
ひっ 日代さん？
You okay?
（海崎）平気？
Y-Yes. Sorry.
あ はい すみません
The crowd got to me again.
また人に酔ってしまいました
少し ここで
時間つぶしていこっか
Let's rest here a while.
はあ… はい
Okay.
よかったですね 狩生さん
I'm really glad for Kariu-san.
カズ君も
And Kazu-kun.
Yeah.
（日代）実は 狩生さんも今日—
The truth is, Kariu-san was also
going to ask Kazu-kun out today.
カズ君に告白するつもりで
いたんです
Because Kazu-kun might be
going to a different college.
（日代）“カズ君と別の大学に
なってしまうかも”と
She said if that happened,
she'd regret not saying anything.
“だったら 言わないと
後悔するから”と…
そっか 狩生も…
Oh, wow. Kariu, too.
When I heard that,
（日代）私はそれを聞いて—
離れる日が来ると分かっていて
好きになるなんて—
I thought that falling in love
when you knew you'd have to part
ムダではないかと思いました
seemed pointless.
But when I saw them together, I was
happy for them from the bottom of my heart.
でも さっき
お２人の様子を見て—
心底よかったなと思いました
Maybe worrying about future partings so much
あとの別れを気に病んで—
その時 その時の幸せを
捨ててしまうのは—
that you miss out on happiness
in the present is a waste.
もったいないのかもしれませんね
（夜明）海崎さんに
関わった すべての人から—
Everyone you dealt with
will forget about you.
海崎さんの記憶は消えます
（海崎）そうだよね
Maybe so.
いつか離れる日が—
Someday, we'll part. Maybe be forgotten.
忘れられちゃう日が
来るかもだけど—
But we're living in the moment.
でも—
俺たちが生きてるのは
今なんだから…
だから…
So...
Hishiro-san, make lots of friends,
日代さんも
たくさん友達 作って—
素敵な恋もして—
fall madly in love,
いっぱい
今しかない時を楽しんでね
and enjoy every moment to the fullest.
Yes. I'll try.
はい 頑張ります
All I can do is cheer her on.
（海崎）俺には 日代さんを
応援することしかできない
She'll forget all about me.
俺に関する記憶は消える
If all her memories are about me,
俺との思い出ばかりに
してしまったら—
then she'll have no memories
of this year left.
日代さんの高３の思い出が
ぽっかり欠けてしまう
日代さんが頑張る 高校生活を—
I'll vanish one day.
I can't rob her of the life
she's fighting so hard to have.
いつか消える俺が
奪っちゃいけない
I was just wondering
if there's anyone you like.
今 好きな子とか
いねえのかなって
Someone you're always with.
気づけばいつも
一緒にいるなって子とか
誰かに取られたら嫌だなとか
You don't want anyone taking her away.
You wanna hold hands.
手をつなぎたいなとか
キスしたいなとか
You wanna kiss her.
（日代）海崎さん？
（海崎）あっ
Kaizaki-san?
That's not it.
（海崎）違う…
You just find it cute that a high schooler's
awkwardly but earnestly trying to change, right?
不器用に
健気に頑張ってる高校生を—
かわいく思ってるだけだったら
Like watching a kid sister grow up?
妹みたいな感覚で…
海崎さん？
Kaizaki-san?
Come to your senses!
（海崎）目を覚ませ
しっかりしろ
Get it together!
Hishiro-san's life will go on,
これから先の日代さんの人生に—
and I...
俺は—
いないんだから…
...won't be there.
（海崎）帰ろっか
Let's go!
（日代）あ あ はい…
Okay.
Sorry.
すみません
もう回復したと
思ってたんですが—
I thought I'd recovered.
まさか こけるとは…
I didn't imagine I'd trip.
よかった 転ばなくて
Thank goodness.
I'm glad I caught you.
You okay? Not gonna trip again?
（海崎）大丈夫？ また転ばない？
I'm fine.
大丈夫です
You sure?
ホントに？
If you're that worried,
（日代）そんなに心配なら…
（海崎）ん？
then let me take your arm.
腕を 貸してください
Ryo offered me his.
了は気軽に貸してくれましたよ
ぷっ くっ あははは ははは どうぞ
Go ahead!
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
Someday we'll have to part.
（海崎）いつか離れる日が—
忘れられちゃう日が
来るかもだけど…
And I'll be forgotten.
But...
だけど…
俺は ずっと忘れないよ
I won't ever forget you.
Yes. I won't forget you, either.
（日代）はい…
私も—
忘れません
Kaizaki-san, you suck!
（小野屋）海崎さんのヘタレ！
Even though Senpai
showed you how to link arms!
先輩が 腕まで組んでみせたのに！
（夜明）いや あれ提案したの
小野屋だったよね？
Wait, that was your idea, though.
ReLIFE Experiment Report
Anyway, I've got a good report
to write today.
ともあれ
今日もいい報告書が書けそうだ
やっぱり 海崎さんは
私が見込んだとおりの人でした
I knew it!
Kaizaki-san's the man I thought he was!
Yep. He managed to get Kariu-san
and Oga-kun together.
（夜明）そうだね
あの狩生さんたちを
くっつけちゃったんだし
（小野屋）
そっちも そうなんですけど
Well, yeah, but he also...
Never mind.
何でもないです
If she's with Kaizaki-san,
Hishiro-san, too...
海崎さんがいれば
きっと日代さんも…
Well, that's up to you. Since you'll be
taking over as her support next term!
それは ２学期から—
日代さんのサポート担当になる
小野屋次第だよ
Right! I'll do my best!
（小野屋）はい 頑張ります！
Kaizaki Arata causes change
in those around him.
（夜明）海崎新太によって
周りの人間は 変わり始める
This is a direct result of his own actions,
それは 積極的に
人に関わろうとした—
彼自身の行動の結果であり—
his drive to get involved
with the people near him.
That, more than anything,
proves his ReLIFE is going well.
それこそが—
彼のリライフが
順調であることの—
紛れもない証拠である
Hishiro-san, what's that?
（海崎）日代さん それ
カメラ機能を 初めて使いました
I used the camera for the first time.
It came out blurry.
ブレブレですけど
へえ いつの間に
When did you take that?
Fireworks may vanish, but memories remain.
花火は消えてしまいますが
思い出は残ります
Arata! Save me!
（大神）新太 助けて！
（海崎）わっ えっ
（狩生）助けてって
あんた 人を鬼みたいに！
"Save me"?
What am I, some sort of demon?!
あ 日代 今度は負けないからね
Ah, Hishiro! I won't lose this time!
（日代）ぬふふ
海崎さん モテモテですね
Kaizaki-san... you're quite popular.
What?! Is that what this looks like?!
（海崎）これが？
この状況が そんなふうに見える？
A one-year, limited edition of youth.
（海崎）１年限定の青春
I may be an illusion that'll be forgotten...
どうせ忘れられてしまう
幻だとしても—
...but I'll treasure every moment, and enjoy...
一瞬一瞬を大事に—
楽しんで生きてみよう
あはは
...my ReLIFE!
（海崎）この リライフを！